

SKILLS JAVA SE SPRING BOOT REACT JS NEXTJS PYTHON SQL **MICROSOFT OFFICE INTELIJ IDEA NETBEANS MONGO DB GIT AND GITHUB BUSINESS ANALYSIS**

DAVID OLUWASEUN AREEGBE

SENIOR DEVELOPER

TEL: +2349015061171

EMAIL: davidcodes2005@gmail.com

GITHUB: https://github.com/davidcodes17

OBJECTIVES

Backend developer with 5+ years of leading terms and delivering high-quality software on time and within budget. Key goal: Writing long lasting, platform independent and reliable code, I would like to work with you and help you convert your ideas to possibilities

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

WEST AFRICAN EXAMINATION COUNCIL (WAEC)

KINGDOM MODEL COLLEGE(NIGERIA) (2019-2022)

OND COMPUTER SCIENCE

THE REDEEMERS COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT (RECTEM) (2023 - PRESENT)

JAVA CERTIFICATE

GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED (1ST OCT 2020)

BUSINESS ANALYSIS CERTIFICATE

COVEN WORKS & AMERICAN CENTER FOR ARIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

WORK EXPERIENCE

GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED (2017 - 2020)

PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR

WORKED AS A PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR RASING YOUNG DEVELOPER WITH DIFFERENT PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES AND SOFTWARE PACKAGES LIKE HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JAVA, PYTHON, REACT JS, MSOFFICE, ETC

GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED (2021 - PRESENT)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

WORKED AS A SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BUILDING LONG LASTING, PLATFORM INDEPENDENT AND RELIABLE SOFTWARES WHICH WERE SOLD TO OTHER BUSINESS

REFRENCES

ENOCH OLUJIDE .A.

CEO GODSOST SYSTEMS LIMITED

MORONKE TITILAYO .A.

CEO OLOBE CLASSIK

OLUWASEUN EMMANUEL

CEO ALHERI'S COLLECTIONS